-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
本字幕由cece&飞飞字幕组倾情奉献
制作：飞飞
校对：西西
How.I.Met.Your.Mother
Season 1 Episode 15
老爸老妈浪漫史 第一季 第15集
孩子们, 你们可能不了解Marshall叔叔
Kids,something you might not
know about your uncle Marshall
他一直很善长玩游戏
is that he's always been
good at games.
我是说, 简直无敌
I mean,unbeatable.
Gin!
Yahtzee!
扑克!
Poker!
你不需要在赢的时候叫唤"扑克"
You don't have to shout out
"poker" when you win.
我知道 只是为了好玩
I know.It's just fun to say.
我们最后一致认为Marshall
应该主持我们的游戏之夜
We all finally agreed Marshall
should be running our game nights
而不是和我们一起玩
instead of playing in them.
结果他理解成――
"发明自己的游戏"
Which he took to mean,
"invent your own game."
就叫"胡诌沼泽"
It's called "Marsh-gammon."
它包含了所有好游戏特征
It combines all the best features
of all the best games
"糖果岛" "我从没" "智力游戏"
Candyland,I never,Pictionary.
- 还有双陆棋
- 不 双陆棋很烂
- Backgammon,obviously.
- No.Backgammon sucks.
我只取了其中的精华部分"胡诌"
I took the only good part of
backgammon,the "gammon",
然后把剩下的丢回垃圾车
and I left the rest of it in
the trash where it belongs.
我真高兴Victoria来了
I'm so excited Victoria's coming.
我去再拿点酒
I'going to go get another round.
好吧, 我想说点今晚的基本规则
Okay,I want to lay down some
ground rules for tonight.
Barney, 我很喜欢Victoria
Barney,I actually like
Victoria...a lot,
所以别说什么尴尬的话...
so don't say anything embarrass...
什么也别说
don't say anything.
伙计们还有, 我没有告诉Victoria
And guys,I haven't exactly
told Victoria
我曾经喜欢Robin
that I used to have a kind
of thing for Robin,
所以我们要避免...
so if we could just avoid the...
嗯, 嗯, 嗯
多荒唐啊
well,well,well.
How rich.
你要我在你女朋友面前
You make me promise to be
on my best behavior
谨言慎行
around your girlfriend,
但, 你从第一天就对她撒谎了
yet,you have been lying
to her since day one.
打扰
Excuse me.
嗨 义肢商店?
Hi.Leg Warehouse?
对, 我朋友Ted需要点东西站住脚
Yeah,my friend Ted needs
something to stand on.
没有可以让他站住脚的东西吗?
So,nothing for him to stand on?
好吧, 还是非常感谢
Okay,and thanks so much.
Ted, Victoria难道不应该知道
Ted,doesn't Victoria deserve
to know that
你曾喜欢Robin吗?
you once had the hots for Robin?
我有点想把"回马枪"的故事讲出来了
I have half a mind to tell
the story of the re-return.
别 我让你保证过的
No.I-I swore you to
secrecy on that.
噢, 我嗅到了脏东西
Oh,I am smelling dirt.
"回马枪"是什么?
What is the story of the re-return?
没什么 什么都不是
Nothing.It's nothing.
说到挖猛料
And speaking of digging up dirt,
你们能不能保证别为难Victoria?
can I count on you two to
behave around Victoria?
我们? 我们能做什么?
Us? What would we do?
听着, 呃, 你们老是表现的像家长
Look,um,you guys have always
been like the parents
我父母都还在
that I still have and,
事实上, 我搬来这就是为了避开他们
in fact,moved here to get away from.
无论如何, 我们今晚能跳过审问
However,could we skip the
traditional interrogation
新女朋友的惯例吗?
of the new girlfriend tonight?
- 好吧
- Fine.
- Fine
谢谢
Thank you.
- 我去看看Robin
- 好的
- I should go help Robin.
- Okay.
- 嘿
- Hey.
你今晚得和Victoria相处,你感觉还好吧?
So,are you going to be okay hanging
out with Victoria tonight?
噢, 当然 她很不错
Oh,sure.She's great.
噢, 怎么?
Oh,what?
因为我说过我喜欢Ted吗?
Because of the whole thing
here I said I liked Ted?
别 Victoria很不错
No.Victoria's great.
她很风趣, 她无拘无束
她很不错
She's fun,she's free-spirited,
she's great.
我说了"她很不错"太多次了吗, 是吗?
I said,"she's great" too many
times,didn't I?
你一定很讨厌那个贱人
You must really hate the bitch.
但是如果你在薄荷糖森林附近
but if you roll an even number
的时候掷了偶数
while adjacent to the peppermint forest,
那么你就"Marshall出局"
你所有的筹码都回到罐子里
then you "Marshall out,"and all
your chips go into the pot,
还有记住, 如果你说了"什么?"
and remember,if you ever ask
the question "what?,"
那... 你就得罚酒
Then...you got to drink.
- 懂了吗?
- 别, 别...
- Got it?
- No,no...
好吧, 好吧, 别, 别, 我们开始吧
你们很快就会了
okay,okay,no,no,we'll just start,
you guys'll pick it up.
新来的先掷
Newbie goes first.
- 掷
- 好吧
- Roll.
- Okay.
3!
Three!
你的自述
You got autobiography.
现在, 你得真实的回答一个
Now,that's where you have to
answer a personal question
关于你约会史的私人问题才能前进
about your dating life truthfully i
n order to move on.
Marshall, 拜托
Marshall,come on.
嘿, 是她自己掷了3的
Hey,she's the one who rolled
a three.
Victoria
"你曾经在一段感情里不忠吗?"
Victoria,"have you ever cheated
while in a relationship?"
哇, 好问题
Wow,good question.
- 听着, 你不需要回答这问题
- 没事
- Look,you don't have to answer that.
- It's okay.
呃, 嗯,大学我曾陷入一段非常讨人厌的关系里
Um,well,I was in a really crappy
relationship in college,
在一晚的派对上我吻了他
and I wound up kissing this guy
at a party one night,
我感觉很糟糕
and I felt terrible about it,
所以, 我去跟他说清楚然后分手了
so,I came clean,and we broke up.
Victoria, 这是一个诚实而且成熟的答案
Victoria,that was an honest and mature answer.
你可以提前到达糖山
You may advance to the gumdrop mountains.
那么 Victoria,你有没有"回了又回"去找过那个家伙吗?
So Victoria,did you ever re-return to this guy?
什么?
What?
你说了"什么"
你得罚一杯!
you said what,
you got to drink!
噢, Barney, 顺便说下
Oh,Barney,by the way,
我去过那幢82街新楼的一个派对
T went to a party in that new building on 82nd,
主人说她认识你
and the host said she knew you.
她叫什么来的?
What is her name?
Shannon?!Shannon,Shannon...
不, 不记得任何一个Shannon
no,don't remember any Shannon.
是吗?
Really?
嗯, 她给我了一个录象带让我...
Well,cause she gave me a video tape to give...
录象带在哪?
where's the tape?
好的 我去拿
Fine.I'll get it.
酷, 好的,你知道, 随便什么时候都可以
Cool,okay.You know,whenever.
好了, Robin, 到你了
Okay,Robin,your roll.
5!
five!
又一个自述...
Another autobiography...
在你左边的游戏者
for the player to your left,which...
- Victoria!
- 当然
- Of course.
Victoria, 在Ted之前你有
Victoria,"how many boyfriends
did you have
交往过几个男朋友?
before you started dating Ted?"
等下, 卡片上真的有写"Ted"吗?
Wait,the card actually says "Ted?"
好吧, 呃, 嗯
Okay,uh,well,
男朋友,我想我只有2个
boyfriends,I guess I've only had...two.
假正经
Prude alert.
嗯...
Well...
只是真正交往的男朋友
that's serious boyfriends.
之间我也有和其他家伙在一起
I've dated other guys in between.
噢, 荡妇!
Oh,slut alert!
噢, 太好了, 拿来了
oh,great,here it is.
谢谢, Lily
你真讨人喜欢
Thanks,Lily.
You're a peach.
噢, 哇, 看啊
oh,wow,look at that.
Robin停在了巧克力沼泽
Robin landed on the chocolate swamp.
我得到了5个筹码
That's five chips for me.
谢谢!
Thank you!
终于有人搞懂了胡诌沼泽
Finally somebody understands
Marsh-gammon.
Barney, 录象带上有什么?
Barney,what was on that tape?
糟糕你永远也不会知道了
Too bad you' never find out.
噢, 该死!
Oh,damn it!
如果我只给了你个假录象带
If only I'd given you a fake tape
而把真的藏在包里
and hidden the real tape in my purse.
噢, 等等 我就是那样做了
Oh,wait.That's exactly what I did.
- 什么?!
- 罚酒!
- What?!
- drink!
耶, 你表现的太怪异了
Yeah,you were acting so weird
about it,
我把Ted的毕业录象拿给你了
I gave you Ted's graduation
tape instead.
那么, 我们应该看吗?
So,should we pop it in?
- 把它给我, 把它给我...
- 播那盘带子, 播吧, 播它!
- Give it to me,give it,give me...
- play the tape,play it,play it!
Ted!
好吧, 好吧
Fine,fine.
你们最好播不出来
You can not play it.
Shannon! 我爱你!
Shannon!I love you!
我那么爱你
I love you so much.
我们一起来改变世界吧?
What about us changing the world together?
别告诉我你忘记了
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
我知道我还没有
I know I haven't.
will I ever see another rainbow?
Will an eagle ever soar through
this tempest of woe?
Baby,please don't go!
there's a thief in the palace,
she's stolen all my love
there's a thief in the palace
and she's...
你打他手机了吗?
Did you try his cell phone?
有啊, 我留了两条言
Yeah,I left two messages.
我找过雪茄吧 激情美洲豹
I checked the cigar club,the lusty leopard.
他消失了
He's off the grid.
嘿, 伙计们, 在干嘛?
Hey,guys,what up?
Barney, 你去哪了?
Barney,where have you been?
是啊, 我们-我们都感到很抱歉
Yeah,we're-we're really sorry
about that.
是啊, 很抱歉
Yeah,so sorry.
但是说真的, 那录象带是怎么回事?
But seriously,what was up with the tape?
别, 别, 留下
拜托, Barney
No,no,stay.
Come on,Barney.
拜托 留下!
抱歉
Come on.Stay!
I'm sorry.
我不想谈这个
I don't want to talk about it.
那是我这辈子最尴尬
It was the most embarrassing,
最丢脸的事
and humiliating thing that ever happened to me.
嗯, 我们都有尴尬的故事
Well,we all have embarrassing stories.
有时候谈谈也有好处
Sometimes it's good to talk about it.
噢, 是吗?
Oh,really?
那为什么不告诉我们
你最难堪的时刻呢, Marshall?
Then why don't you tell us your
most humiliating moment,Marshall?
告诉我有多好
Show me how good it is.
好吧
All right.
那天我顺路去Lily幼儿园打个招呼
I was stopping by Lily's kindergart
class to say hi,
但他们都出去休息了
but they were all at recess.
我很想尿尿, 所以我走进了教室的厕所
I really had to pee,so I went
into the class's restroom.
那里的圈圈看起来不好瞄
It was a-a smaller target
than I'm used to,
所以我决定蹲下来
so I figured I should sit down.
我没有注意到的是,
那是一个共用的浴室
What I didn't realize was,
it was a shared bathroom.
我真希望当时把裤子提上了
I wish I'd pulled up my pants.
孩子们还是叫他搞笑屁股
the kids still call him funny butt.
好吧
Okay.
我告诉你们我的故事
I'll tell you my story.
信不信由你们
我的生活不是一开始就象现在这样棒
Believe it or not,
I was not always as awesome as I am today.
那年是1998
It was 1998.
我刚从大学毕业
I was just out of college,
我和我的女朋友在一间咖啡屋工作
and I was working at a coffeehouse
with my girlfriend.
我的女朋友... Shannon
My girlfriend...Shannon.
Yeah, you were meant for me
Yeah,you were meant for me
and I was meant for you
谢谢
Thank you.
好的
All right.
我喜欢你的歌声, Barney
I love your singing,Barney.
我爱你, Shannon
And I love you,Shannon.
和你一起加入国际和平组织
这将成为传奇性事件
joining the Peace Corps with you
is gonna be legendary.
我知道
I know.
离我们去尼加拉瓜只有短短3周了
Only five short weeks till
we're down in Nicaragua.
嘿, 低脂拿铁打包
Hey,nonfat latte to go.
真会点, 伙计
Mellow order,bro
真会点
mellow order.
伙计, 那是你女朋友吗?
不错, 值得击掌!
Dude,that your g-friend?
All right,high five!
抱歉, 我习惯用V字手势
Sorry,I only give high twos.
随便吧
Whatevers.
当你把她放倒的时候
As long as you're nailing that.
看看你说的 放倒?
Listen to you. That?
你要知道, 女人不是物品
You know,women aren't objects.
她们是人
They're human beings.
还有, Shannon和我认为应该等到我们结婚的时候
And FYI,Shannon and I have decided
to wait till we're married.
你能在我的幻想杂志中读到
You can read about it in my zine.
嘿, 小辫子, 听我说
Hey,haircut,right here.
打开你智慧的库门
我送你一些
Open up your knowledge basket,
cause here it comes.
去他的狗屁感情
Forget that touchy-feely crap.
有钱就有马子
You get money,you get laid.
就这么牛
End of discussion.
我为你感到痛惜, 伙计
I feel sorry for you,man.
我们井水河水啦, 老兄
Peace out, hombre.
西装男
suits.
5周后, 我们准备好去国际和平
Five weeks later,we were all set
to leave for the Peace Corps.
唯一的问题是...
Only problem was...
她没有出现
she never showed up.
她一直没出现吗?
she never showed?
那后来怎么样了?
So,what happened next?
你们知道吗? 这是个错误
You know what?This was a mistake.
那谁把自己的最丢脸的故事说出来怎样?
what if somebody else told their
most humiliating story?
噢, 我知道怎么决定谁说
Oh,I know just how to decide who.
你把游戏带到酒吧来了?
You brought the game to the bar?
虽然Ted领先很多
我们也不该放弃啊
Well,we're not quitting just
cause Ted's so far ahead.
我领先?
I was winning?
好吧 我来说
fine.I'll go next.
我当时正在做一个关于出租司机
的电视直播报道
I was doing a report on live TV
about a hansom cab driver.
不要听掉进马粪的故事!
Not the slipping-in-horse-poop
story!
对, 我们都知道那个
Yeah,we all know that one.
好了, 这样怎么样?
Okay,how about this?
我来告诉你们我最丢脸的故事
I will tell you my most
humiliating story.
耶, Victoria, 十分期待
Yeah,Victoria,way to step up!
好了, 它包括了真心话大冒险
Okay,it involves a game of
truth or dare,
一软瓶的糖汁用于冰激凌的点缀的
a squeeze-bottle of marshmallow
ice cream topping,
我父母的老人俱乐部浴缸
and the hot tub at my grandparents'
retirement community.
孩子们, 我告诉你们
很多不该说的故事
Kids,I tell you a lot of
inappropriate stories,
但是别想我会告诉你们这个
but there's no way in hell
I'm telling you this one.
但别担心
那故事也不是那么棒
Don't worry,though,
it wasn't that great.
这是最棒的故事!
That is the greatest story ever!
- 噢 我的天那!
- 哇, 哇!
- Oh my god!
- Wow,wow!
Victoria, 我认为你的故事...
Victoria,I deem your offering...
值得
worthy.
我的传奇故事...
My saga...
继续下去
continues.
我回咖啡屋去找Shannon
I went back to the coffeehouse
to find Shannon.
Barney
Barney.
宝宝熊, 你去哪了?
Sugar bear,where were you?
噢, 我很抱歉
Oh,I'm sorry.
我爸爸不让我去
My dad won't let me go.
但尼加拉瓜人民需要我们!
But the Nicaraguans need us!
但是他仍然在经济上支持我, 还有...
It's just,he's still supporting me,and...
听着, 他马上就要来和我谈这个了
look,he's coming by soon to talk about it,
我觉得你应该自己上路
but I think you should go on
without me.
Shannon, 没有...
Shannon,there is no...
Barney, 这是你的梦想
Barney,it's your dream.
只有两年
我知道我们可以做到
It's only two years.
I know we can make it.
当我走开的时候, 我意识到
Shannon成年了
As I walked away,I realized
Shannon was an adult.
她的父亲不能控制她的生活
Her father couldn't control her life.
我要回去说服他
I had to go back and confront him.
她正在和她爸爸争吵着
She was in the middle of a heated
argument with her dad.
什么?!
What?!
我们都得罚酒了
now we all got to drink.
噢, 我的天
后来怎样了?
oh,my god.
What happened next?
- 我不知道, 伙计们
- 好吧, 好吧
- I don't know,guys.
- Okay,okay.
Marshall的妈妈给我们寄来饼干...
Marshall's mom sent us cookies...
Lily, 别!
Lily,no!
为了团队, Marshall
为了团队
For the team,Marshall,
for the team.
嘿, Eriksen夫人, 我是Lily
Hey,mrs.Eriksen,it's Lily.
谢谢你如此美味的饼干
Thank you so much for the delicious cookies.
蛋黄酱 真的吗?
Mayonnaise.Really?
真想不到
Never would have guessed.
嗯, 我会代你给Marshall一个吻的
Well,I will definitely give
Marshall a kiss for you.
好的 保重
Okay.Take care.
噢, 糟糕 我妈送来饼干吗?
Oh,crap.My mom sent cookies?
是啊 我真希望我们有只狗
那就可以不用扔掉了
Yeah.I wish we had a dog,
so they wouldn't go to waste.
那么所有的地方都是我们的了
So we've got the whole place
to ourselves.
我在考虑地板激情
I'm thinking floor sex.
听起来合理
Sounds reasonable.
噢, 地板很凉
Oh,floor's cold.
把你妈妈做的毛毯抓来
Grab that afghan your mom made.
从头到尾吗?
The whole time?
从... 头... 到尾
The... whole... time.
Barney, 那对我们两来说都很难堪
Barney,that was really embarrassing
for both of us.
我们应该赢得了一大块故事
We just earned a huge chunk of story.
好 我刚到哪了?
Right.So where was I?
噢, 对 Shannon在和她爸爸热吻
Oh,yeah.Shannon was sucking face
with her dad.
怎么能和你爸爸...?
How can...with your dad?
虽然我们不该评判别人
I mean,I know judge not lest
ye be judged,
但好恶心啊!
but gross!
Barney, 那不是我爸爸
Barney,that's not my dad.
他叫Greg
His name's Greg.
我和他一起几周了
I've been seeing him for a few weeks.
我原希望你走了就好了
I was hoping you'd just leave,
我们就可以避免这样了
and we could avoid all this.
我们分手了吗?
We're breaking up?
但是和国际和平怎么办?
But what about the Peace Corps?
这些只不过是人生的一个阶段
Yeah,all this granola business,
it was just a phase.
Greg更成熟
Greg's older.
他有事业
He's successful.
他给我买了所有这些东西
He buys me all this cool stuff.
但我爱你
But I love you.
但他有艘船
But he has a boat.
你应该去和平队
You should go to the Peace Corps
然后忘了我
and forget about me.
我没有走
I didn't go.
那晚, 我录了录像带送给Shannon
That night,I recorded my video
and mailed it to Shannon.
直到一周后我才见到她
I didn't see her until a week later.
篮子里有糖
There's sugar in the basket.
Shannon!
Shannon, 你回来了!
Shannon,you came back!
我只是来领我最后的工资
I'm just picking up my last paycheck.
你有没...
Did you...
你有没收到我的录象带?
did you get my tape?
噢, 她收到了录象带
Oh,she got the tape.
你? 是你?
You?It was you?
我能再看见另一条彩虹吗
Will I ever see another rainbow
穿上西装!
Suit up!
噢, 可怜的东西
oh,you poor thing.
故事还没完
The story's not over.
我还见过一次Shannon
I did see Shannon one more time.
- 什么时候?
- 抱歉
- When?
- sorry.
你得告诉我们
You've got to tell us.
我不知道
I don't know,
我想得用最后一个故事来帮我下
I think I might need one last
story to get me through it.
好吧
Fine.
绿色睾丸的故事
The green testicle story.
那是我在大学时候正玩着终极飞盘
So I was playing ultimate frisbee in college
有一个光着脚而且脚趾特别长尖的家伙...
and there was this barefoot dude
with weirdly sharp toenails...
噢, 拜托, Ted!
oh,come on,Ted!
你知道我想听哪个故事
You know what story I want to hear.
在这里的每个人都有勇气说出事实
Everyone else here has manned up
tonight and told the truth.
为什么你不行?
Why can't you?
你是对的
You're right.
Victoria, 我很抱歉我没告诉你这个
Victoria,I'm sorry I haven't
told you this yet,
但是之前, 我曾喜欢Robin
but a while back,I was kind
of into Robin.
事实是, 我们第一次约会那天
In fact,on our first date,
我可能说了 "我爱你"
I might have said,"I love you."
很容易理解, 她吃惊了我离开了
Understandably,she freaked out
and I left.
但不幸的是, 那一晚并不是完结点
But unfortunately,the night
did not end there.
我们和司机Ranjit一起在酒吧喝酒
We all ended up at the bar
with our cab driver Ranjit.
为这带劲的一晚!
To one hell of a night!
我喝了很多酒
and I drank...a lot.
你们觉得我应该吻她吗?
So you guys think I should
have kissed her?
嗯, 我跟你们说
Well,I'll tell you what,
我现在就去吻她
I'm gonna go kiss her right...now.
好! 去吧!
Yes!Do it!
上车去
To the cab.
喂?
Hello?
有人在外面吗?
Is someone out there?
你吐了然后跑了
you ralphed and ran?
我以为你是"93年起免吐王"
I thought you were vomit-free
since 93.
是骗人的?
So that was a lie?
你回来找我了
You re-returned for me.
这太贴心了
That's really sweet.
尽管你某种程度上
毁了我定做的Scherbotsky擦鞋垫
Though you kind of ruined my
customized Scherbotsky doormat.
- 抱歉
- 没事
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Victoria, 我知道这一定...
Victoria,I know this must be...
是啊 确实
yeah.It kinda is.
哇, Ted, 你对了
Wow,Ted,you were right.
你不该讲这个故事
You shouldn't have told that story.
但你赢得了我的故事结尾
But you did earn yourself the
right to the end of mine.
我们快进到8年后
We fast-forward eight years into the future.
等等, 8年
Wait,eight years,
那不是, 那不就是今年
that's,that's this year.
Marshall, 不仅是今年
Marshall,not only is it this year,
是今晚
it's tonight.
嗨
Hi.
- Barney?
- 嗨, Shannon
- Hi,Shannon.
- 你来干什么?
- 你听着
- What are you doing here?
- Just listen.
当你为了Greg离开我后
When you left me for that guy Greg,
改变了我
it changed me.
现在我是这样的
Now I'm this.
我-我知道这很疯狂
I-I know this is crazy.
只是, 你曾经是我生命的一大部分
It's just,you were once such
a big part of my life.
但你现在却不知道我是怎样的
And it just seemed insane that
you didn't know who I am now.
所以我就来了
So here I am.
然后她告诉了我她的事
And then she told me about her life.
她和Greg约会了一段时间然后分了
She and Greg dated for a while
and then split up.
但是有点震惊的是
Shannon现在是妈妈了
But here's the real kicker:
Shannon's a mom.
她的孩子叫Max
She has a little kid named Max.
这太疯狂了
That's crazy.
那本可能是我的孩子
That could have been my kid.
但取而代之, 我有什么?
But instead,what do I have?
我一辈子就只有银行里的存款
My whole life's some money
in the bank,
衣橱里的西装和一打一夜情
some suits in my closet and
a string of one-night stands.
嘿 别这样
Hey.Come on.
她选了她的生活方式,你的是另一种方式
I mean,just because her life went
one way and yours went another,
但并没有让你的生活更糟
it doesn't make your life
any worse.
我的生活棒透了!
My life rocks!
钱, 西装和性
Money,suits and sex.
这是我愉快的眼泪!
These are tears of joy!
我可能被困在狭小的公寓里
I could be cooped up
in some tiny apartment
给乳臭未干的小鬼换尿布
changing some brat's poopy diapers.
但取而代之的是,我仍行走在这精彩的世界 24-7-365!
But instead,I'm out in the world
being awesome 24-7,365!
你让我避开了子弹, 大块头
You let me dodge a bullet,big guy.
另外, 再给点精华之中的精华
Plus,here's the mini-cherry
on top of the regular cherry
我的精彩生活中的精华
on top of the sundae of awesomeness
that is my life.
我和Shannon谈过后, 我上了她
After Shannon and I talked,I nailed her.
- 不是
- 是
- Nope.
- Yeah.
- 不是
- 是
- Nope.
- Yeah.
抱歉 我不信
Sorry. no buy it.
你在说谎
You're making it up.
你只是在试图掩饰真相
You're just trying to cover the fact
你确实有一刻对自己产生了怀疑还有...
that you actually had a profound
moment of doubt about yourself and...
噢, 天那
oh,my god.
噢,Barney
Oh,Barney
这摄象头很不错吧, 哈?
video's pretty good on this phone,huh?
你电话开着在吗?
Is your phone on?
噢, 没有 只是要过会才能待机
Oh,no.It just takes a while to power down.
哟, 恶心 别放了
Ew,gross.Just stop it.
女士们, 先生们... Ted
ladies,gentlemen...Ted.
这是一个精彩的夜晚
This has been a wonderful evening.
我挖出了你们的猛料
I got great dirt on all you guys.
我让Ted讲述了"回马枪"的故事
I got Ted to tell the re-return.
我终于上了Shannon!
I finally nailed Shannon!
告诉她我明天打给她
Told her I'd call her tomorrow.
耶, 棒
Yeah,right.
我还发现我的生活到底有多棒
And I rediscovered just how
awesomely awesome my life is.
不带一片云彩
Peace out,hombres!
我想游戏之夜Barney赢了
I think Barney just won game night.
我们花那么多工夫试图掩盖一部分事实
We spend so much effort trying to
keep parts of our lives hidden,
甚至对我们最亲近的朋友
even from our closest friends.
这是少有的敞开心怀的时刻
But thosrare times when we do open up,
令人惊奇的是这些故事结局都那么相似
it's amazing how minor those secrets all end up seeming.
Right? Right?
Right?Right?
You've got
to want
to rearrange and keep it
off the record
当然, 那天不是每个秘密都戳破了
of course,not every secret was told that night.
但正是有秘密才会有故事发生
But that's getting ahead of the story.
--------------------------
(*^__^*) cece&飞飞字幕组(*^__^*)
-=cece&飞飞=-
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
制作: 飞飞
校对: 西西
组长：cece
-=终其一生，只爱西西=-
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第1季 第15集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother
Season 1 Episode 15